

# Amanda Fletcher Team Leader + Client Servicing

+ E-Commerce + CRM

#### **About Me**

Successful Client Servicing and Retail Associate with Five years of experience addressing customer requests & concerns with a strong Operations & E-commerce Background. Expert at providing relevant information and options to successfully resolve issues. Upbeat and energetic handling difficult situations through resourcefulness and adaptability.

## My Contact

amandafletcher123.af@gmail.com

**(**+91 99304 25696

Bengaluru, Karnataka

English, Hindi

## **Hard Skill**

- Customer Relation Management
- E-Commerce
- Team: Development & Happiness
- Store Operations & Inventory Management
- Strategic Planning and execution
- MS-Excel
- **CRM Flows**

## **Soft Skill**

- · Customer service Oriented
- Adaptability
- Patience and Self-control
- Interpersonal and Clear Communication
- Decision making
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

- Ironwood Global Academy, Mumbai Post Graduate Diploma in Sports Management Completed in 2019
- Smt. M.M.K. College of Commerce & Economics, Mumbai

**Bachelor of Commerce** Completed in 2017

Smt. M.M.K. College of Commerce & Economics, Mumbai Pre-University Course Completed in 2014

# **Professional Experience**

### Indiabulls Consumer Finance Ltd. | Customer Care Collection Officer

October, 2017 - June, 2019 Key responsibilities:

**Gustomer Relationship Management - Assisted over 18K** customers, of which nearly 3.5K customers have been successful in securing personal loans to meet various needs

- Part of pilot batch providing personal assistance to customers of the Dhani app(Dhani is a first of its kind personal loan app that disburses instant loans to a customer's bank account) since its launch in Oct 2017
- Top 10 Performer for six months, among a pool of 100 customer service representatives

Regularly assisted Senior Managers in improving the app by suggesting new features that reflect client needs and performing user acceptance testing

Training - 15 new joiners and brought them quickly up-to-speed on the procedures and best practices

#### Decathlon Sports Limited, Pvt Ltd | CRM Referent | Team Leader

July, 2019 - August, 2021

Key responsibilities: CRM Referent

Coordinated with operations staff to resolve service problems to boost customer satisfaction. Collaborated with peers and other business areas to leverage best practices. Assisted with marketing strategy development to increase public awareness and customer engagement.

Reduced expenses by renegotiating vendor contracts to eliminate waste & boost cost savings

Introduced clients to available online resources and services to increase convenience.

Monitored metrics and developed actionable insights to improve efficiency and performance.

#### September, 2021 - November, 2022

- Key responsibilities: Team Leader
- Managed the P&L and Vendor management
- Compiled product and customer data to generate informed profit projections. Recruited, managed & motivated 6 members to the retail team to give every customer positive and memorable experiences.
- · Conducted training and mentored team members to promote productivity and commitment to friendly service.

## <u>Achievements</u>

First place in NBA Jam India 2016

Mumbai Represented University for 2014 - 2016 Basketball Recognition - Successful Project 2021

opening in 7 days(COVID Time)